stretchclock.com 2010-11-29

# StretchClock Privacy Policy

StretchClock was built from the ground up with your privacy in mind.   

## Privacy in a Nutshell:

We do not collect or store any personal information unless you give us express consent.

We do use Logs, Cookies, and Clear images, to monitor site traffic and report on our usage statistics. We may report on your usage information bundled together with everyone else’s usage information. This “aggregate” usage information may be shared with our advertisers and other Third Parties (such as the media).

## Privacy in Detail

### Information Collection & Use

**Log Files**

As is true of most Web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files.  This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. 

We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. 

We do not link this automatically-collected data to personally identifiable information.

We use a third-party tracking service “Google Analytics” that uses cookies to track non-personally identifiable information about visitors to our site in the aggregate (e.g. usage and volume statistics for the purpose of providing enhancements to the website.)

**Cookies**

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies on this site. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site.

We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies.  We use session cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site. A session ID cookie expires when you close you browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser’s “help” file.

Persistent cookies enable us to track and target interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. 

If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some areas of our site, such as Stretches, contests or surveys, will be limited.

This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by StretchClock.com only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. (See the “[Third Party Advertisers](http://www.shareasale.com/r.cfm?B=83688&U=234221&M=12798)” section) 

**Clear Gifs (Web Beacons/Web Bugs)**

We sometimes employ a software technology called clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons/Web Bugs), that help us better manage content on our site by informing us what content is effective.

Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of Web users.  In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user’s computer hard drive, clear gifs are embedded invisibly on Web pages and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. 

We do not tie the information gathered by clear gifs to our customers’ personally identifiable information. 

** ** **Surveys or Contests**

From time-to-time we may provide you the opportunity to participate in contests or surveys on our site.  If you participate, we will request certain personally identifiable information from you. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information.  The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code). 

We use this information to notify contest winners and award prizes or personalize the site (in the case of anonymous information collected in surveys)

We will not share the personally identifiable information you provide through a contest or survey with other third parties unless you give us permission.

**Heal-A-Friend**

StretchClock’s Tell a Friend feature is completely anonymous. If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, you will be launching your own email program. Therefore, StretchClock will have no knowledge of your email address or your friend’s email address.

**ShareThis**

StretchClock uses a service called ShareThis. If you use the "ShareThis feature" then you should consult their [Privacy Policy](http://sharethis.com/privacy)

**Profile**  

We store information that we collect through cookies, log files, clear gifs, and/or third party sources to create a “profile” of your preferences.  We do not tie your personally identifiable information or your purchasing history to information in the profile.

We do not share your profile with other third parties.  We may share your profile in aggregate form only.

**Email Subscriptions**

We will not rent, sell or trade your personal information (including your email address) with anyone unless you tell us to. We use aWeber for our email list service. They are pioneers in permission based email policies. Here is their [privacy policy](http://www.aweber.com/privacy.htm)

### Information Sharing and Disclosure

**Aggregate Information (non-personally identifiable)**

We share aggregated demographic information about our user base for the purposes of publicity and to generate advertising revenue. This information does not identify individual users. We do not link aggregate user data with personally identifiable information. 

**Personally identifiable information**

We DO NOT share any Personally Identifiable Information with Third Parties unless you have given express consent (for example: you may ask us to provide your shipping address to a third party if you win a contest.)

### Third Party Advertisers

Some of the ads appearing on this Web site are delivered to users by our advertising partners (Commission Junction, LinkShare, and ShareASale).

Our advertising partners may use cookies and/or clear GIFs on this site, which allow it to recognize a user's cookie when a user visits this site. The information that our advertising partners collect is not personally identifiable. 

For more information about our third-party advertiser, or to learn more about the choices available to you regarding this anonymous information, please  see the privacy policies of:

### Links to Other Sites

This Web site contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by us. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. 

We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. 

This privacy statement applies only to information collected by this Web site. 

### Changes in this Privacy Statement  

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. 

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently.  If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page.

### Contact Us 

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us.
